Register of the William Patrick Clark papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- United States National Security Council File, 1982-1983
  - 1982 alphabetical correspondence
    - Wick, Charles Z. (Box-folder 59: 3)
    - Y (Box-folder 59: 4)
    - Z (Box-folder 59: 5)
    - Zelaya, Jorge L. (Guatemalan ambassador) (Box-folder 59: 6)
    - Zumwalt, Elmo R., Jr. (Box-folder 59: 7)
  - 1983 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 59: 8-9)
    - Abrams, Elliott (Box-folder 59: 10)
    - Abshire, David M. (Box-folder 59: 11)
    - Allen, Richard V. (Box-folder 59: 12)
    - Annenberg, Walter H. (Box-folder 59: 13)
    - Armstrong, Anne (Box-folder 59: 14)
    - B (Box-folder 60: 1-2, Box-folder 59: 15-16)
    - Baker, Howard H., Jr. (Box-folder 60: 3)
    - Baldrige, Malcolm (Box-folder 60: 4)
    - Barnett, Frank R. (Box-folder 60: 5)
    - Bea, Carlos (Box-folder 60: 6)
    - Bengelloun, Ali (Moroccan ambassador) (Box-folder 60: 7)
    - Bennett, W. Tapley, Jr. (Box-folder 60: 8)
    - Bernstein, Myron S. (Box-folder 60: 9)
    - Bish, Milan David (Box-folder 60: 10)
    - Brooks, Claudia (Box-folder 60: 11)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew (Box-folder 60: 12)
    - Buckley, James L. (Box-folder 60: 13)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr. (Box-folder 60: 14)
    - Burns, Arthur F. (Box-folder 60: 15)
    - Bush, George (Box-folder 60: 16)
    - C (Box-folder 60: 17, Box-folder 61: 1-3)
    - Carlucci, Frank C. (Box-folder 61: 4)
    - Casey, William J. (Box-folder 61: 5)
    - Casmir, Fred L. (Box-folder 61: 6)
    - Chavez Mena, Fidel (Salvadoran foreign minister) (Box-folder 61: 7)
    - Cheney, Richard (Box-folder 61: 8)
    - Cherne, Leo (Box-folder 61: 9)
    - Chiang, Ching-kuo (president of Taiwan) (Box-folder 61: 10)
    - Cline, Ray S. (Box-folder 61: 11)
    - Coleman, George (Box-folder 61: 12)
    - Committee in Support of Solidarity (Box-folder 61: 13)
    - Crane, Kent (Box-folder 61: 14)
    - Crozier, Brian (Box-folder 61: 15)
    - D (Box-folder 62: 1-2)
    - Dailey, Peter H. (Box-folder 62: 3)
    - Davis, Jeffrey C. (Box-folder 62: 4)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 62: 5)
    - Dingell, John D. (Box-folder 62: 6)
    - Dole, Robert (Box-folder 62: 7)
    - Drury, Allen (Box-folder 62: 8)
    - E (Box-folder 62: 9)
    - East, John P. (Box-folder 62: 10)
    - F (Box-folder 62: 11-12)
    - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr. (Box-folder 63: 1)
    - Finch, Robert H. (Box-folder 63: 2)
    - Findley, Paul (Box-folder 63: 3)
    - Ford, Gerald R. (Box-folder 63: 4)
    - Fowler, H. L., III (Box-folder 63: 5)
    - Freedman, Jonathan (Box-folder 63: 6)
    - G (Box-folder 63: 7-8)
    - Garwood, Ellen Clayton (Box-folder 63: 9)
    - Gavin, John (Box-folder 63: 10)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 63: 11)
    - Graham, Billy (Box-folder 63: 12)
    - Graham, Daniel O. (Box-folder 63: 13)
    - Gray, Edwin J. (Box-folder 63: 14)
    - Gray, Robert Keith (Box-folder 63: 15)
    - H (Box-folder 64: 1-2, Box-folder 63: 16)
    - Harman, Phillip (Box-folder 64: 3)
    - Hart, Jeffrey (Box-folder 64: 4)
    - Hatch, Orrin G. (Box-folder 64: 5)
    - Helms, Jesse (Box-folder 64: 6)
    - Henze, Paul B. (Box-folder 64: 7)
    - Hermes, Peter (West German ambassador) (Box-folder 64: 8)
    - Hewitt, William A. (Box-folder 64: 9)
    - Hickel, Walter J. (Box-folder 64: 10)
    - Hill, Ben (Box-folder 64: 11)
    - Hugel, Max (Box-folder 64: 12)
    - I (Box-folder 64: 13)
    - Irvine, Reed (Box-folder 64: 14)
    - J (Box-folder 64: 15)
    - James, E. Pendleton (Box-folder 64: 16)
    - Jepsen, Roger W. (Box-folder 64: 17)
    - Jordan, Amos A. (Box-folder 64: 18)
    - K (Box-folder 64: 19-20)
    - Kassebaum, Nancy Landon (Box-folder 65: 1)
    - Khashoggi, Adnan M. (Box-folder 65: 2)
    - Kim, Dae Jung (Box-folder 65: 3)
    - Kishi, Nobusuke (Box-folder 65: 4)
    - Kissinger, Henry A. (Box-folder 65: 5)
    - Klestil, Thomas (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 65: 6)
    - Korologos, Tom C. (Box-folder 65: 7)
    - L (Box-folder 65: 8-9)
    - Laghi, Pio (apostolic delegate) (Box-folder 65: 10)
    - Laxalt, Paul (Box-folder 65: 11)
    - Lee, Luke T. (Box-folder 65: 12)
    - Lehrman, Lew (Box-folder 65: 13)
    - Linowitz, Sol M. (Box-folder 65: 14)
    - Lodge, John Davis (Box-folder 65: 15)
    - Lofton, John (Box-folder 66: 1)
    - Luce, Gordon C. (Box-folder 66: 2)
    - Lugar, Richard G. (Box-folder 66: 3)
    - M (Box-folder 66: 4-7)
    - McCaffrey, Stephen C. (Box-folder 66: 8)
    - Mansfield, Mike (Box-folder 67: 1)
    - Mattingly, Mack (Box-folder 67: 2)
    - Mayer, Charles T. (Box-folder 67: 3)
    - Medici, Marino de (Box-folder 67: 4)
    - Michel, Robert H. (Box-folder 67: 5)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II (Box-folder 67: 6)
    - Moore, John Norton (Box-folder 67: 7)
    - Morris, Robert (Box-folder 67: 8)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 67: 9)
    - Moynihan, Daniel P. (Box-folder 67: 10)
    - Munn, James S. (Box-folder 67: 11)
    - Murchison, David C. (Box-folder 67: 12)
    - N (Box-folder 67: 13)
    - Nauer, Barbara (Box-folder 67: 14)
    - Negroponte, John D. (Box-folder 67: 15)
    - Newman, Frank (Box-folder 67: 16)
    - Nicholson, George (Box-folder 67: 17)
    - Nicolaides, Philip (Box-folder 67: 18)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 67: 19)
    - Nofziger, Lyn (Box-folder 67: 20)
    - Nunn, Sam (Box-folder 67: 21)
    - O (Box-folder 67: 22)
    - Orfila, Alejandro (Box-folder 68: 1)
    - O'Sullivan, Tadhg (Irish ambassador) (Box-folder 68: 2)
    - P (Box-folder 68: 3-4)
    - Padilla, Hernan (Box-folder 68: 5)
    - Pell, Claiborne (Box-folder 68: 6)
    - Percy, Charles H. (Box-folder 68: 7)
    - Pfaltzgraff, Robert L., Jr. (Box-folder 68: 8)
    - Q (Box-folder 68: 9)
    - Quayle, Dan (Box-folder 68: 10)
    - R (Box-folder 68: 11-12)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 69: 1)
    - Richardson, Frank K. (Box-folder 69: 2)
    - Robinson, Gilbert A. (Box-folder 69: 3)
    - Rockefeller, David (Box-folder 69: 4)
    - Rostow, Eugene V. (Box-folder 69: 5)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Box-folder 69: 6)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald (Box-folder 69: 7)
    - Ruppe, Loret Miller (Box-folder 69: 8)
    - Rush, Kenneth (Box-folder 69: 9)
    - Rusher, William A. (Box-folder 69: 10)
    - S (Box-folder 69: 11-14)
    - Schweiker, Richard S. (Box-folder 70: 1)
    - Serong, F. P. (Box-folder 70: 2)
    - Serrano-Elias, Jorge (president of Guatemala) (Box-folder 70: 3)
    - Shakespeare, Frank (Box-folder 70: 4)
    - Shultz, George P. (Box-folder 70: 5)
    - Smith, William French (Box-folder 70: 6)
    - Specter, Arlen (Box-folder 70: 7)
    - Staar, Richard F. (Box-folder 70: 8)
    - Sugahara, Kay (Box-folder 70: 9)
    - T (Box-folder 70: 10)
    - Teller, Edward (Box-folder 70: 11)
    - Thapa, Bekh Bahadur (Nepalese ambassador) (Box-folder 70: 12)
    - Theberge, James D. (Box-folder 70: 13)
    - Thurmond, Strom (Box-folder 70: 14)
    - Trent, Darrell M. (Box-folder 70: 15)
    - U (Box-folder 70: 16)
    - V (Box-folder 70: 17)
    - Verity, C. William, Jr. (Box-folder 70: 18)
    - W (Box-folder 70: 19-20, Box-folder 71: 1)
    - Walker, John T. (Box-folder 71: 2)
    - Walker, June G. (Box-folder 71: 3)
    - Watt, James (Box-folder 71: 4)
    - Weisman, Steven R. (Box-folder 71: 5)
    - Whetstone, Frank A. (Box-folder 71: 6)
    - Wick, Charles Z. (Box-folder 71: 7)
    - Williams, Edward Bennett (Box-folder 71: 8)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 71: 9)
    - Wirthlin, Richard B. (Box-folder 71: 10)
    - Wohlstetter, Albert (Box-folder 71: 11)
    - Y (Box-folder 71: 12)
    - Z (Box-folder 71: 13)
    - Zumwalt, Elmo R., Jr. (Box-folder 71: 14)
  - Subject file
    - Arms control, 1983 (Box-folder 71: 15)
      Memoranda
    - Austria, 1983 (Box-folder 71: 16)
      Statement, memorandum and printed matter
    - China, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 71: 17)
    - Grenada, 1983 (Box-folder 71: 18)
      Draft article
    - Haig, Alexander--Resignation as Secretary of State, 1982 (Box-folder 71: 19, Box-folder 72: 1-2)
      Press coverage
    - Ireland, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 72: 3)
      Correspondence, memoranda and press releases
    - Korea, 1981 (Box-folder 72: 4)
    - Law of the sea, 1982 (Box-folder 72: 5)
      Printed article
    - Leaks, 1982 (Box-folder 72: 6)
      Memorandum
    - McFarlane, Robert C., 1982 (Box-folder 72: 7)
      Press release
    - Meese, Edwin, III, 1982 (Box-folder 72: 8)
      Letter and printed article
    - National Security Council structure and organization, 1962-1982 (Box-folder 73: 1)
      Notes, memoranda, charts and printed matter
    - National Security Decision Directive 2 (NSDD-2: National Security Council Structure), 1981 (Box-folder 73: 2)
      Annotated text and drafts
    - National Security Decision Directive 15 (NSDD-15: U.S. Relations with the USSR), 1983 (Box-folder 73: 3)
      Text
    - National Security Decision Directive 19 (NSDD-19: Protection of Classified National Security Council and Intelligence Information), 1982 (Box-folder 73: 4)
      Text and memorandum
    - National Security Decision Directive 66 (NSDD-66: East-West Economic Relations and Poland-Related Sanctions), 1982 (Box-folder 73: 5)
    - National Security Study Directive 11-82 (NSSD 11-82: U.S. Relations with the USSR), 1982 (Box-folder 73: 6)
    - Poland, 1982 (Box-folder 73: 7)
    - Rancheros Visitadores, 1982 (Box-folder 73: 8)
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1983 (Box-folder 73: 9)
      Annotated speech by Reagan
    - Reed, Thomas C., 1982 (Box-folder 73: 10)
    - Shultz, George P., 1983 (Box-folder 73: 11)
      Interview transcript
    - Sontag, Susan, 1982 (Box-folder 73: 12)
    - South Africa, 1982 (Box-folder 73: 13)
      Printed matter
    - Weinberger, Caspar, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 73: 14)
      Memorandum, speech and interview transcript
  - Memoranda by Robert C. McFarlane, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 73: 15)
  - Miscellaneous memoranda and notes, circa 1981-1983 (Box-folder 73: 16, Box-folder 74: 1-3)
  - Chronological press coverage file
    Printed matter, including some annotations and accompanying memoranda
    - 1982 January (Box-folder 74: 4)
    - 1982 February (Box-folder 74: 5)
    - 1982 March (Box-folder 74: 6)
    - 1982 April (Box-folder 74: 7)
    - 1982 May (Box-folder 74: 8)
    - 1982 June (Box-folder 74: 9)
    - 1982 July (Box-folder 75: 1)
    - 1982 August (Box-folder 75: 2)
    - 1982 September (Box-folder 75: 3)
    - 1982 October (Box-folder 75: 4)
    - 1982 November (Box-folder 75: 5)
    - 1982 December (Box-folder 75: 6)
    - 1983 January (Box-folder 75: 7)
    - 1983 February (Box-folder 75: 8)
    - 1983 March (Box-folder 75: 9-10)
    - 1983 April (Box-folder 75: 11-12)
    - 1983 May (Box-folder 76: 1)
    - 1983 June (Box-folder 76: 2)
    - 1983 July (Box-folder 76: 3)
    - 1983 August (Box-folder 76: 4)
    - 1983 September (Box-folder 76: 5)
    - 1983 October (Box-folder 76: 6)
    - 1983 November (Box-folder 76: 7)
  - Department of State press clipping compilations
    - 1982 January (Box-folder 76: 8, Box-folder 77: 1-2)
    - 1982 February-April (Box-folder 77: 3)
  - White House news summary compilations, 1982 (Box-folder 77: 4)
  - Clippings and serial issues, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 78: 1-5, Box-folder 79: 1-5)
    Mainly relating to Reagan administration and U.S. foreign relations
  - Miscellaneous travel vouchers, 1982 (Box-folder 80: 1)
  - Resignation as National Security Adviser, 1983 (Box-folder 80: 2)
    Letter of resignation and press coverage
- United States Department of the Interior File, 1983-1985
  Papers of William P. Clark as United States Secretary of the Interior, 1983-1985
  - Appointment as Secretary of the Interior, 1983
    - General (Box-folder 80: 3)
      Announcement and personnel documents
    - Memoranda and notes (Box-folder 80: 4)
    - Financial disclosure statement (Box-folder 80: 5)
    - Review of California judicial decisions by Clark made by the Department of the Interior's Office of the Solicitor (Box-folder 80: 6-8)
    - Statements by Clark to the U.S. Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources in conjunction with its confirmation hearings (Box-folder 81: 1)
    - Submissions by Clark to the U.S. Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources in conjunction with its confirmation hearings (Box-folder 81: 2-4)
    - Testimony by others in U.S. Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources confirmation hearings (Box-folder 81: 5)
    - U.S. Senate Committee on Energy and Natural Resources confirmation hearing transcripts, 1983 November 1-2 (Box-folder 82: 1-4)
    - U.S. Senate action on confirmation (Box-folder 82: 5)
      Includes letters by Congressmen, Senate floor debate, Committee on Energy and Natural Resources report, and rollcall vote
    - Press coverage
      - General (Box-folder 83: 1-4)
      - Betty Medsger Village Voice critical article (Box-folder 83: 5)
        Includes memoranda and statements in response
    - Congratulatory letters (Box-folder 85: 1-2, Box-folder 84: 1-6)
  - Biographical file
    - General, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 85: 3)
      Press releases, summary of accomplishments, memoranda and certificates
    - Interviews of Clark, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 85: 4-5)
      Printed transcripts
    - Press coverage, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 85: 6, Box-folder 86: 1-5)
  - Briefing books, 1983 (Box-folder 87: 1-2)
  - Appointment book, 1984 (Box-folder 87: 3)
  - Speeches and events file
    Correspondence, memoranda, notes, briefing materials, press releases, itineraries, programs, press coverage and speeches
    - California Farm Bureau Federation meeting, Anaheim, California, 1983 November 28 (Box-folder 87: 4)
    - Citizens for America meeting, Washington, D.C., 1983 December 6 (Box-folder 87: 5)
    - National Wildlife Federation conference, Washington, D.C., 1983 December 7 (Box-folder 88: 1, Box-folder 87: 6)
    - Ford's Theatre supper, Washington, D.C., 1983 December 7 (Box-folder 88: 2)
    - Keep America Beautiful awards luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1983 December 8 (Box-folder 88: 3)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies Southern California Leadership Forum, Los Angeles, California, 1983 December 13 (Box-folder 88: 4)
    - American Legislative Exchange Council briefing, Washington, D.C., 1984 January 9 (Box-folder 88: 5)
    - National Association of Manufacturers issue breakfast, Washington, D.C., 1984 January 10 (Box-folder 88: 6)
    - Department of the Interior employees meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 January 11 (Box-folder 88: 7)
    - Outer Continental Shelf Policy Committee meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 January 12 (Box-folder 89: 1)
    - The Indomitable Teddy Roosevelt film showing, Washington, D.C., 1984 January 18 and 26 (Box-folder 89: 2)
      Includes introductory talking points
    - Appalachian Trail conference ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1984 January 26 (Box-folder 89: 3)
    - American Mining Congress annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 January 31 (Box-folder 89: 4-5)
    - United States Senate Youth Program meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 January 31 (Box-folder 89: 6)
    - Department of the Interior Black History Month observance, Washington, D.C., 1984 February 1 (Box-folder 89: 7)
    - National Parks Service/Coleman Company reception, Washington, D.C., 1984 February 8 (Box-folder 89: 8)
    - Visit to New Mexico, 1984 February 9-10 (Box-folder 89: 9-10)
    - New Mexico State Legislature address, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1984 February 10 (Box-folder 90: 1)
    - Department of the Interior employees meeting, Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1984 February 10 (Box-folder 90: 2)
    - New Mexico legislators dinner, Santa Fe, New Mexico, 1984 February 10 (Box-folder 90: 3)
    - Visit to California, 1984 February 11-13 (Box-folder 90: 4)
    - Visit to meet with former President Jimmy Carter, Moultrie, Georgia, 1984 February 19-20 (Box-folder 90: 5)
    - Wolf Trap Foundation meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 February 27 (Box-folder 90: 6)
    - National Recreation and Park Association forum, Arlington, Virginia, 1984 February 28 (Box-folder 90: 7)
    - Visit to California, 1984 March 3-4
      - General (Box-folder 90: 8)
      - Entertainment of President Rudolf Kirchschlager of Austria at Clark ranch (Box-folder 90: 9)
    - U.S. Geological Survey briefing, Reston, Virginia, 1984 March 9 (Box-folder 90: 10)
    - National Park concessioners meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 March 12 (Box-folder 90: 11)
    - Republican women officeholders briefing, Washington, D.C., 1984 March 12 (Box-folder 90: 12)
    - Mining and Reclamation Council luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1984 March 13 (Box-folder 90: 13-14)
    - American Petroleum Institute meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 March 13 (Box-folder 91: 1)
    - Reception for Dick Harris, Washington, D.C., 1984 March 15 (Box-folder 91: 2)
    - National Wildlife Federation meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, 1984 March 17 (Box-folder 91: 3-4)
    - Cecil D. Andrus portrait unveiling ceremony, Department of the Interior, 1984 March 20 (Box-folder 91: 5)
    - North American Wildlife and Natural Resources Conference, Boston, Massachusetts, 1984 March 26 (Box-folder 91: 6)
    - Visit to Arizona and California, 1984 March 27-April 1 (Box-folder 92: 1)
    - Central Valley Project tour, Arizona, 1984 March 27 (Box-folder 92: 2)
    - Reagan-Bush fundraiser, Phoenix, Arizona, 1984 March 27 (Box-folder 92: 3)
    - Brad Gates testimonial luncheon, San Juan Capistrano, California, 1984 March 28 (Box-folder 92: 4)
    - Hispanic businessmen briefing, San Diego, California, 1984 March 28 (Box-folder 92: 5)
    - Reagan-Bush reception, San Diego, California, 1984 March 28 (Box-folder 92: 6)
    - National Public Lands Advisory Council meeting, San Diego, California, 1984 March 29 (Box-folder 92: 7)
    - San Diego Union Editorial Board meeting, San Diego, California, 1984 March 29 (Box-folder 92: 8)
    - Rotary Club luncheon, San Diego, California, 1984 March 29 (Box-folder 92: 9)
    - California Republican Assembly meeting, Sacramento, California, 1984 March 31 (Box-folder 92: 10)
    - National Ocean Industries Association annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 2 (Box-folder 92: 11)
    - Central Arizona Project press conference, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 3 (Box-folder 92: 12)
      Includes transcript
    - National Legal Center for the Public Interest Corporate General Counsel meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 4 (Box-folder 92: 13)
    - Environmental Defense Fund dinner, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 6 (Box-folder 93: 1)
    - Ford's Theatre gala, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 8 (Box-folder 93: 2)
    - World Wildlife Fund luncheon, New York, New York, 1984 April 9 (Box-folder 93: 3)
    - National Park Foundation meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 13 (Box-folder 93: 4)
    - Reclamation World's Fair Exhibit, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 18 (Box-folder 93: 5)
    - American Recreation Coalition meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 19 (Box-folder 93: 6)
    - Denny Smith fundraiser breakfast, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 24 (Box-folder 93: 7)
    - Golden State Roundtable luncheon, Washington, D.C., 1984 April 26 (Box-folder 93: 8)
    - Visit to Alaska, 1984 April 29-May 2
      - General (Box-folder 93: 9)
      - Briefing book (Box-folder 93: 10)
    - Chamber of Commerce luncheon, Anchorage, Alaska, 1984 April 30 (Box-folder 94: 1-2)
    - Visit to California, 1984 May 2-6 (Box-folder 94: 3)
    - East Bay Regional Park District 50th anniversary dinner, Oakland, California, 1984 May 3 (Box-folder 94: 4)
    - University of California at Santa Barbara major donors annual dinner, Santa Barbara, California, 1984 May 5 (Box-folder 94: 5-6, Box-folder 95: 1-2)
    - National Forest Products Association annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 May 7 (Box-folder 95: 3-5)
    - U.S. Presidential Delegation visit to the 35th anniversary commemoration of the Berlin Airlift, Berlin, Germany, 1984 May 10-13 (Box-folder 96: 1)
    - Berlin Senat commemoration ceremony, Berlin, Germany, 1984 May 11 (Box-folder 96: 2)
    - Kongresshalle rededication ceremony, Berlin, Germany, 1984 May 12 (Box-folder 96: 3)
    - U.S. Presidential Delegation dinner, Berlin, Germany, 1984 May 12 (Box-folder 96: 4)
      Includes toast
    - Renner Institute meeting, Vienna, Austria, 1984 May 15 (Box-folder 96: 5-7)
    - Visit to Oklahoma, Texas and California, 1984 May 20-22 (Box-folder 97: 1-2)
    - Mickey Edwards fundraiser, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 1984 May 20 (Box-folder 97: 3)
    - Republican National Hispanic Assembly breakfast, San Antonio, Texas, 1984 May 21 (Box-folder 97: 4)
    - American Association of Petroleum Geologists convention, San Antonio, Texas, 1984 May 21 (Box-folder 97: 5)
    - Western Governors Conference, Palm Springs, California, 1984 May 21 (Box-folder 97: 6)
    - National Strategic Materials and Minerals Advisory Commission meeting, Department of the Interior, 1984 May 25 (Box-folder 97: 7)
    - Visit to Montana, Colorado, Illinois and Michigan, 1984 May 30-June 4 (Box-folder 97: 8, Box-folder 98: 1)
    - Montana State Republicans fundraiser, Billings, Montana, 1984 May 30 (Box-folder 98: 2)
    - Montana Stockgrowers Association meeting, Miles City, Montana, 1984 May 31 (Box-folder 98: 3-5)
    - Bear Trap Canyon Wilderness dedication, Montana, 1984 June 1 (Box-folder 98: 6)
    - International Congress on Irrigation and Drainage, Fort Collins, Colorado, 1984 June 2 (Box-folder 99: 1-3)
    - Outdoor Writers Association of America conference, Traverse City, Michigan, 1984 June 4 (Box-folder 99: 4)
    - U.S. Chamber of Commerce interview and breakfast, Washington, D.C., 1984 June 7 (Box-folder 99: 5)
    - Republican National Committee meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 June 7 (Box-folder 99: 6)
    - Visit to Tennessee, 1984 June 14-15 (Box-folder 99: 7)
    - Great Smoky Mountains National Park golden anniversary, celebration, Tennessee/North Carolina border, 1984 June 15 (Box-folder 100: 1-2)
    - National Coal Association meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984 June 19 (Box-folder 100: 3-4)
    - Wolf Trap Farm Park for the Performing Arts Filene Center dedication, Vienna, Virginia, 1984 June 20 (Box-folder 100: 5)
    - Visit to California, 1984 June 21-25 (Box-folder 101: 1, Box-folder 100: 6-7)
    - American Legislative Exchange Council annual meeting, San Diego, California, 1984 June 22 (Box-folder 101: 2)
    - Fresno area water leaders briefing, Fresno, California, 1984 June 22 (Box-folder 101: 3)
    - Charles Pashayan fundraiser, Fresno, California, 1984 June 22 (Box-folder 101: 4)
    - Villanova Preparatory School anniversary celebration, Ojai, California, 1984 June 23 (Box-folder 101: 5)
    - Duck stamp 50th anniversary exhibit, Washington, D.C., 1984 June 26 (Box-folder 101: 6)
    - Michigan and Ohio major donors briefing, Washington, D.C., 1984 June 27 (Box-folder 101: 7)
    - World Wildlife Fund/Agency for International Development project signing ceremony, Department of the Interior, 1984 June 28 (Box-folder 101: 8)
    - Visit to Louisiana, 1984 July 9-10 (Box-folder 101: 9)
    - Rivers and River Management Symposium, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1984 July 10 (Box-folder 101: 10)
    - Reefs Task Force meeting, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1984 July 10 (Box-folder 101: 11)
    - Citizens for America meeting, White House, 1984 July 11 (Box-folder 101: 12)
    - Visit to Kentucky, 1984 July 12 (Box-folder 101: 13)
    - National Campers and Hikers Association convention, Beach Bend Campground, Kentucky, 1984 July 12 (Box-folder 101: 14)
    - Visit to Tennessee and North Carolina, 1984 July 13-14 (Box-folder 101: 15)
    - American Association of Petroleum Landmen annual meeting, Nashville, Tennessee, 1984 July 13 (Box-folder 101: 16)
    - Albuquerque Indian school property transfer ceremony, Washington, D.C., 1984 July 23 (Box-folder 101: 17)
    - Frank Wolf fundraiser, McLean, Virginia, 1984 July 23 (Box-folder 101: 18)